A C-section, for example, cuts someone between the top and the bottom.
例如，剖腹产将一个人从上到下切开。
We need to re-energize that.
我们需要重新激活它。
The uterus is actually a concentration of posterior parietal peritoneum.
子宫实际上是后壁腹膜的集中。
In this whole phase of development, in the peritoneum,
在整个发育阶段，在腹膜中，
at the moment when all this develops, I also have a posterior concentration,
当所有这些都在发育时，我也有一个后方的集中，
a power, like that, that comes to recenter itself.
一种力量，就这样，重新集中。
And it's almost a terminal fulcrum.
这几乎是一个终末支点。
I have both an embryonic fulcrum and then I have a finality fulcrum.
我既有一个胚胎支点，又有一个终极支点。
of development. And it's also
发育的。这也很
important to bring them back because that's where we bring you.
重要的是要带回它们，因为那是你被带到的地方。
I come underneath. I take
我来到下面。我把
the whole belly in my hands.
整个腹部都放在我的手中。
And I must try to keep my hands well
我必须努力让我的手保持
relaxed. I take my time.
放松。我花时间。
I can tell you
我可以告诉你
that there is a breath
有一个呼吸
that is a little too high. It's a request
有点太高了。这是一个
for discretion. The warmth,
谨慎的要求。热量，
it's an exchange between
是组织之间的
the tissues. That is, it's an exchange
交换。也就是说，是她和我之间的
between her and me. So she's willing
交换。所以她愿意
to start giving me information. Right now,
开始给我一些信息。目前，
The tissue, in any case, is getting a little defensive.
组织，无论如何，它有点防御。
The rather low area for her, here, begins to relax, to
对她来说，这里较低的区域开始放松，
position itself.
定位。
I have more exchanges, whereas in the upper part, I don't yet have
我有更多的交换，而上半部分，我还没有
my homogeneity.
我的均匀性。
My idea is to find a homogeneous state again.
我的想法是恢复均匀状态。
There, it's starting, now, there's just been a level of warmth.
现在，它开始了，现在它刚刚达到一个热度水平。
Maybe he felt it too.
也许他也感觉到了。
But it's as if all of a sudden, all the lines of force are
但就好像突然之间，所有的力线都
orienting towards the uterine area.
指向子宫区域。
It's as if there's a concentration reforming towards that area.
就好像有一个集中重新形成到那个区域。
So it's as if she could reintegrate her nest.
所以就好像她可以重新融入她的巢穴。
It can be better.
这样可能会更好。
We're going to help her return to her inner home.
我们将帮助她回到她的内在家园。
Someone who is attached to their land.
一个依恋于自己土地的人。
Now, I can enter into something much more global.
现在，我可以进入更全面的东西。
I'm starting now to make contact with the whole body
我现在开始与整个身体接触
which I didn't have, I was fragmented before
我以前没有的，我以前是碎片化的
there's a therapeutic process that has just started
那里有一个治疗过程刚刚启动
that is, I'm starting to feel little by little the integration
也就是说，我开始一点一点地感受到整合
towards the ethereal zone, maybe you can perceive that
进入以太区域，也许你能感觉到
I'm starting to have greater homogeneity
我开始有更大的一致性
between my left hand and my right hand
在我的左手和我的右手之间
when you have someone who has had a hysterectomy
当您遇到做过子宫切除术的人时
The whole dynamic changes and you know what it develops?
整个动态都改变了，你知道他发展了什么吗？
A buffalo hump.
一个野牛驼峰。
There, it's working on a lot of rebalancing zones here.
现在，它正在这里重新平衡许多区域。
It's really almost a tissue point.
这几乎是一个组织点。
There, now, it's really starting to work.
现在，它真的开始起作用了。
There, I'm starting to have another level coming.
现在，我开始有另一个层次的到来。
It gathers in the earth and it releases a lot of tissues
它聚集在地球中，并释放出许多组织
because it also works in the synchronous development patterns.
因为它也在同步发展模式中工作。
In everything that is...
在所有这些中...
relationship develops. I really give support points, a great support point on
报告正在发展。我真的提供了支撑点，一个大的支撑点
the whole system
整个系统
where it forces the diaphragm to work differently, to
它迫使膈肌以不同的方式工作，去
seek other spaces, other
寻找其他空间，其他
openings. I show him here the hepatic, splenic,
开口。我在这里给他展示了肝脏、脾脏、
sigmoid,
乙状结肠，
Mesenteric, there, now, it's completely relaxed.
肠系膜，现在，他完全放松了。